4icj.com 2019-01-20

# Privacy Policy | jobRank.org

* * *

#### We care about your privacy and we follow the [OECD Privacy Guidelines ](http://www.oecd.org/internet/ieconomy/privacy-guidelines.htm)

## Information about our Organisation and Website

* * *

Our principal activity is: _International directory and search engine of job sites and career resources_  
Our privacy policy covers jobRank.org and its web site:   

Organisation Name: |   jobRank.org  
---|---  
Address: |   Suite 2C, 5 Tambua Street  
City, Zip: |   Pyrmont, 2009  
State: |   NSW  
Country: |   Australia  
Controller: |   F a b i o  F a t u z z o  
  
## Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

* * *

You can access our web site home page and browse our site without registering, signing up or disclosing your personal data.

## The services and links of our web site

* * *

Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. 

## Automatic Collection of Information

* * *

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.  
We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. However third party service providers, such as Google Analytics and Google AdSense, may use cookies and other various tracking technologies.

## Data Collection and Purpose Specification

* * *

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.  
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.  
To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please see below. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.

## Children's Privacy

* * *

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children at any time.

## Disclosure and Visitor Choice

* * *

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.

## Confidentiality and Security

* * *

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorised access 
  * improper use or disclosure 
  * unauthorised modification 
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

## Privacy Compliance

* * *

Our privacy policy is compliant with the following instrument: Australian Privacy Act - www.privacy.gov.au  
In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure.

## Table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used

* * *

The following primary personal data are volunteered by each visitor while filling contact or other forms in our website.  

Primary personal data | Website Technical Administration | Research & Development | Customer Administration | Marketing | Trading in personal data  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Name | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Gender |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Address |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Country | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
E-mail address | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Phone/Fax number | **x** |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Employer/organisation |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Job title |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Personal details |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Physical description |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Family characteristics |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Education and skills |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Life style or personal tastes |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Financial resources |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Online identifiers |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Financial identifiers |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Public bodies identifiers |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Biometrics identifiers |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Racial or ethnic origin |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Political opinions |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Religious or philosophical beliefs |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Trade union membership |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Health/Medical data |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Sex life |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Police or Justice data |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
Other data |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-  |  \-   
  
## Access to the personal data we may hold about you

* * *

You can ask us by email. We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month, although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge. We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.
